Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files, 1876-
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files, 1876-
- Series II. 1900-1999
  - 1970-1979
    - Tucker, Allen J., Jr., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Tulman, Michael J., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Wallach, Marc, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Washington, Lawrence D., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - West, Roger L., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Wilson, John A., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Wolf, David A., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Wright, James M., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Ackerman, David Bruce, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Alexandru, Adrian, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Ansley, James Rawlings, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 25)
      1948-
    - Bandes, John David, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Barra, Michael Joseph, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 27)
      1947-
    - Berman, Eli Michael, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Bird, Richard J., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Brown, Kerry Lee, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 30)
      No class photo; from Israel
    - Butterfield, Timothy J., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Carlson, David Jon, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Coley, David Sherwood, II, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - DeBoer, Henry, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Ford, Donald Eugene, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Goldstein, Martin G., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Leiby, Kent Dean, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Nirschl, David Lee, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Nolan, Thomas E., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Olson, James K., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Powers, Timothy C., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Rogoff, Jay Howard, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Ruksznis, Dennis Alan, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 43)
      1949-
    - Sammons, Myrl Lynn, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Scherline, Eugene D., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Schweitzer, Denise Monica, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Simon, Allan B., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Thompson, Ross William, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Wright, John Jerome, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Yartz, Franklin H., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Zagraniski, Michael J., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Arnold, Stephen Alfred, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Barsanti, Jeanne Ann, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Deans, Margaret Alice, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Dykes, Nathan Leonard, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Evans, David Allen, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Evans, Douglas E., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 57)
      1950-
    - Fagan, Richard Howard, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Glauberg, Aaron Frank, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Harris, Robert Lee, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Jagar, John Eugene, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Kent, Frederick Howe, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Kram, Malcolm Alexander, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Lemieux, Gerald P., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - MacDonald, John Milnner, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - MacNeill, Bradley P., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Morena, Craig Thomas, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Muller, Craig Otto, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Myers, Bernard Samuel, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - Nichols, Robert William, Jr., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 70)
    - Peduzzi, Roger James, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 71)
    - Rees, Roger Elliott, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 72)
    - Rosenfeld, Irving Steven, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 73)
    - Schlafer, Donald Hughes, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 74)
    - Seleen, William Arvid, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 75)
    - Shiriro, Alan Geoffrey, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 76)
    - Travis, Henry J., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 77)
    - Weinstein, Susan, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 78)
    - Westfall, Geoffrey James, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 79)
    - Adams, Stephen Budd, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 80)
    - Aspros, Douglas G., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 81)
      AVMA President 2011-2012
    - Bandes, Robin Truelove Stronk, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 82)
    - Brownie, Cecil Fitz-George, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 83)
    - Bruzgul, Joseph B., Jr., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 84)
    - Charlebois, Andre Joseph, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 85)
    - Cole, John F., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 86)
    - Dattner, Leslie Bruce, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 87)
    - Deutsch, David E., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 88)
    - Efron, Robert Fred, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 89)
    - Fish, Stanley G., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 90)
    - Geasling, Jay W., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 91)
    - Gray, James Heron, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 92)
      1946-2009
    - Greene, Jerry Alan, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 93)
    - Hancock, David Harold, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 94)
    - Hulsander, Ronald W., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 95)
    - King, Linda Rideout, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 96)
    - King, Michael Joseph, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 97)
      1951-
    - Mindlin, Douglas Samuel, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 98)
    - Mirro, Elmer Joseph, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 99)
    - Moffa, John Vincent, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 100)
    - Morris, Alan Stephen, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 101)
    - Morris, Robert A., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 102)
    - O'Neil, John William, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 103)
    - Pane, Robert T., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 104)
    - Rotondo, Kenneth Joseph, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 105)
    - Vail, David George, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 106)
    - Wallace, Lee A., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 107)
    - White, Maurice Edward, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 108)
      No class photo; see also Faculty file
    - Amann, John F., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 109)
    - Appel, Roy, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 110)
    - Bartiromo, Teresa, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 111)
      1951-2013
    - Baum, Sam, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 112)
    - Begg, Susan, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 113)
    - Bloch, Peter William, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 114)
      1952-
    - Bouffard, John, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 115)
    - Brondum, Jack, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 116)
    - Bush, Wende, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 117)
    - Carlson, Robert Walter, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 118)
    - Clark, John A., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 119)
      1951-2008
    - Contino, John Allen, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 120)
    - Daab, Barbara J. B., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 121)
    - Damura, Thomas Anthony, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 122)
    - Deitsch, Philip, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 123)
    - Family, Laurence, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 124)
    - Freyburger, Peter, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 125)
    - Friel, Michael, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 126)
    - Goldberg, Gary, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 127)
    - Gould, Willard Joseph, III, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 128)
    - Gross, John Francis, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 129)
    - Gumaer, Kenneth, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 130)
    - Heslink, Paul I., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 131)
    - Holden, Lawrence, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 132)
    - Holt, Thomas, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 133)
    - Hughes, Judith Childers, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 134)
    - Humphrey, Peter W., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 135)
    - Ingraham, Peter J., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 136)
    - Jacobs, Eric, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 137)
    - Jaworski, Walter, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 138)
    - Johnson, Francis, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 139)
    - Johnson, Jolyon, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 140)
    - Kay, Michael Raynor, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 141)
    - Kittell, John, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 142)
    - Lawless, James Michael, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 143)
    - Marshall, Kent R., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 144)
    - Martorana, Francis, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 145)
    - Morizi, John Louis, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 146)
    - Murphy, Randall, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 147)
    - Nusbaum, Kenneth Eliot, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 148)
    - O'Connor, Robert, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 149)
    - Petro, Susan Bernadette Peckham, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 150)
    - Petro, Russell J., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 151)
    - Phillips, Frances, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 152)
    - Randall, William, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 153)
    - Rogers, Robert A., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 154)
    - Rosser, Edmund, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 155)
    - Rothwell, Thomas Peter, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 156)
    - Schwartz, David J., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 157)
    - Shepherd, William, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 158)
    - Shull, Robert M., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 159)
    - Shultz, Craig E., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 160)
    - Smiley, Daryl, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 161)
    - Smith, Gary E., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 162)
    - Stack, Robert, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 163)
    - Storozum, Sidney H., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 164)
    - Sutton, George F., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 165)
    - Trenka-Benthin, Susan, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 166)
    - Veralli, Paul Joseph, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 167)
    - Valinsky, Victor M., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 168)
      1949-2009
    - Venezia, Lawrence, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 169)
    - Volpini, Lucia, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 170)
    - von Kutzelben, Roy, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 171)
    - Walsh, John M., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 172)
    - Wilderoter, Katharine, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 173)
    - Abernathy, Linda L., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 174)
    - Allen, Charles H., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 175)
    - Austin, Frederick G., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 176)
    - Beekman, Gerard K., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 177)
    - Berkowitz, Jay A., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 178)
    - Bertoldo, Gerald Robert, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 179)
    - Bochino, Mary S., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 180)
    - Brenneman, James Daniel, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 181)
      1949-1991
    - Byer, Linda D., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 182)
    - Carman, Donald Mark, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 183)
    - Chapman, Edward B., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 184)
    - Chuff, Nicholas Cobb, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 185)
    - Comings, Timothy Currier, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 186)
    - Covitz, Jack, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 187)
    - Cruickshank, Robert E., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 188)
    - DeVerna, John Charles, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 189)
    - Ellis, Roger George, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Everitt, Jeffrey I., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Ferry, John W., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Fitzpatrick, Timothy L., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Foley, Mark H., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Gaynor, Faith M., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Gillette, Deborah M., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Griffin, Craig E., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Hajdu, Andrew, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Hall, Jeffrey A., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Hayden, James G., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Helfat, Mark P., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Hoppe, Robert W., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Huntington, Ann Louise, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Jenkins, David H., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Kasprzak, Kenneth, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      Class photo; No Cornell DVM degree
    - Landsman, Clifford, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Levine, Steve B., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Lindsey, Alan, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Lissman, Barry A., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Lubar, Jonathan B., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Lynch, Patrick A., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Makowski, Christine M., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 23)
      1951-2007
    - Manfra, Sandra J., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Miller, Lila T., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Minster, Karl C., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Monroe, Timothy J., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Noga-Driscoll, Maryjean, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Oliver, Ried J., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Perry, Robert W., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Peters, Ronald, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Pointek, Kathleen A., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Randolph, John F., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Reamsnyder, Karen Elizabeth, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Rothermich, Ann R. C., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Sanders, Clark, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Schnabel, Arthur J., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Schwytzer, Donald G., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Shek, William Robert, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Silverman, Steven B., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Solana, Richard Peter, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Tewes, Anton, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Thonsen, William J., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Williams, Craig B., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Wolfthal, David M., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Woods, Rochelle E., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Yarkoni, Uriel, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Yarnell, Gary A., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Babcock, Gary, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Bicknese, Joanne M., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 50)
      1954-
    - Bratton, Myron, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Bratton, Patricia, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Broady, Mark, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Bruno, Dwight, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Cali, Joseph, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Carell, Robert, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Cerf, Dean, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Chamberlain, Thomas, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Clark, Kathleen, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Costlow, David, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Delong, David, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - Diez, Jose, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - Ellis, Laurel, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - Fischer, Jonathan, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - Franklin, Jessica, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 65)
    - Garnes, Dianne, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 66)
    - Gartland, Philip M., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 67)
      19??-1976
      2nd year student killed in avalanche
    - Giaquinto, Francis J. "Frank", 1978 (Box 21, Folder 68)
    - Giaquinto, Mary Wilkes, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 69)
    - Glassman, Peter S., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 70)
    - Goldstein, Mark, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 71)
    - Gregory, Clare, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 72)
    - Guglielmino, Joanna, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 73)
    - Jacobs, Allen, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 74)
    - Jann, Henry, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 75)
    - Johnson, Paul, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 76)
    - King, Peter W., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 77)
    - Knowlton, Brenda, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 78)
    - Lea, Pamela J., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 79)
      1953-
    - Levine, Marc, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 80)
    - Lewis, Steven, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 81)
    - Luckow, Kenneth, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 82)
    - Luckow, Scott, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 83)
    - Lutgens, Gretchen Allen, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 84)
    - Lutgens, Kurt, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 85)
    - Marks, Michael, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 86)
    - Matthews, Nora Starr Baldridge [Baldridge, Nora S.], 1978 (Box 21, Folder 87)
    - McMaster, Carolyn Ann, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 88)
    - McQuade, Joseph, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 89)
    - Merrill, George, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 90)
    - Meyer, Pamela A., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 91)
    - Miller, Richard, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 92)
    - Mintzer, Charles, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 93)
    - Morris, Robert C., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 94)
      19??-1998
    - Moses, Scott, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 95)
    - Nashe, George B., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 96)
    - Naum, Robert, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 97)
    - O'Krepki, James, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 98)
    - O'Leary, Timothy, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 99)
    - Plance, William David, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 100)
    - Pollock, Roy Van Horn, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 101)
    - Rappole, Robert Goodell, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 102)
    - Rath, John, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 103)
    - Schmidt, Marilyn, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 104)
    - Schoen, Allen M., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 105)
    - Schultz, Steven, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 106)
    - Siegel, Martin, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 107)
    - Stoufer, Karen Lafky, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 108)
    - Sullivan, William, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 109)
    - Thompson, Roger, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 110)
    - Tillou, Guy J., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 111)
    - Truffini, Stanley, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 112)
    - Washburn, Patricia A. Evans, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 113)
    - Widrick, Patrina, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 114)
    - Wilhelm, William, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 115)
    - Wilhelmsen, Catherine, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 116)
    - Wilson, Julia, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 117)
    - Wirsig, Victoria, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Wisniewski, Jo-Anne, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Zielinski, Karen, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Axtell, Raymond, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Behr, Melissa J., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Binder, Robert Steven, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Blackmore, Keith N., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Boardman, Crager J., Jr., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Breite, Marshall H., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Burgess, Margaret E., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Cartin, Robert K., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Charpentier, Amy Denise, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Cookingham, Carol A., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Cross, Susan E., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Davis, Eric M., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Demson, Martha V., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - DeVries, Richard A., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Dietze, Amy E., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Dunn, David A., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Dziezyc, Joan, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Ehrlich, James L., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Fenton, Elaine L., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Ferraglio, Susan A., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Ferrante, Pamela L., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Foote, Anita Christine, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Freedman, Philip, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Friedman, Jeff A., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Gardner, Stephen A., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Gearhart, Martha S., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Gerson, Leslie H., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Haibel, George K., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Hardie, Elizabeth Mills, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Hayden, Joan D., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Hershkowitz, Lisa, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Hofmeister, Erik K., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Hotchkiss, Signe K., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Huntington, Barbara F., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Keem, Michael Dennis, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Knox, Alison M., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Kornet, Mitchell Evan, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 40)
      1955-
    - Korten, Peter, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Kreger, Leonard D., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Kuntz, Roger B., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - LeClair, Barbara, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Lengemann, Frederick W., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Levine, Marcia J., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Lin, Kay S., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Llop, Quentin H., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Looby, William C., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Martinisi, Venera J., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Mantell, Dale Dennis, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - May, Samuel A., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - McCormick, Arthur E., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Milligan, Joseph, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - Munschauer, Thomas L., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - Murphy, Michael S., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - O'Shea, James E., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 57)
    - Palermo, Joseph C., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 58)
    - Palmer, George W., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 59)
    - Payne, Richard, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 60)
    - Peterson, Lorraine E., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 61)
    - Prokop, William J., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 62)
    - Roth, Lois, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 63)
    - Sanford, Steven P., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 64)
    - Scipioni, Roberta, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 65)
    - Sozanski, Michael S., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 66)
    - Stein, Richard J., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 67)
    - Strom, Jeffrey S., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 68)
    - Sullivan, Mary A., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 69)
    - Szatkowski, Ellen M., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 70)
    - Tarlach, Natalie, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 71)
    - True, Robert G., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 72)
    - von der Schmidt, Edward, III, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 73)
    - Warner, Neal J., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 74)
    - Williams, Alexandra, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 75)
    - Wolfer, Kevin V., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 76)
    - Zeh, John P., III, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - 1980-1989
    - Arnold, Bette Ann, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 78)
    - Baker, Donald J., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 79)
    - Boothby, Janet M., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 80)
    - Bristol, David G., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 81)
    - Camann, Christine Tecklenburg, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 82)
    - Caravaty, Mark R., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 83)
    - Chafetz, Eric, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 84)
    - Cheever, Holly, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 85)
    - Citek, Gerald J., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 86)
    - Coccari, Philip, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 87)
    - Cogan, Deborah C., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 88)
    - Cohen, Marc, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 89)
    - Conway, Marion Bernadette, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 90)
    - Coren, Alan M., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 91)
    - DeHart, Dorothea A., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 92)
    - Duhamel, Ghislaine "Peggy", 1980 (Box 22, Folder 93)
    - Durland, Robert W., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 94)
    - Edwards, Allen H., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 95)
    - Ellmers, Gorden, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 96)
    - Fettman, Martin J., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 97)
      First veterinarian astronaut in space
    - Gerstman, Buddy B., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 98)
    - Gibson, Mark C., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 99)
    - Griffin, Wayne, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 100)
    - Grodkiewicz, Jeffery Paul, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 101)
    - Guard, Charles L., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 102)
    - Guth, Daniel T., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 103)
    - Hardie, Bradford, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 104)
    - Hays, James T., III, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 105)
    - Huntley, John P., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 106)
    - Huse, Jeffry John, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 107)
    - Irwin, Priscilla S., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 108)
      1945-2007
    - Jacobson, Andrea Elise, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 109)
    - Johnson, Margaret E., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 110)
    - Johnston, Christine, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 111)
    - Kinnarney, Joseph H., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 112)
    - Kornheiser, Kenneth M., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 113)
    - Kramer, Jeffrey M., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 114)
    - Kranz, Mark A., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 115)
    - Kross, Susan B., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 116)
    - Lacour, Anina D., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 117)
    - Laczk, John P., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 118)
    - Law, Karen Dana, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 119)
    - Lesser, Sue Ann, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 120)
    - Lodahl, Claire S., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 121)
    - Maas, Jennifer, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - MacKay, Marianne, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Mainville, Debra C., 1980 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Marder, Brian, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Marienberg, William, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Mattucci, Margarette, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - May, Jonathan Edward, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - McCormick [Davies], Hannah, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - McEntee, Michael Fraser, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - MacNamara, Brian, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Meier, Roderick S., 1980 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Meyer, Robert E., 1980 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Mills, Walter Steven, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Moran, Jamie, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Munson, Linda, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      19??-2010
    - Nizolek, Joseph Thomas, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Palmeter, Andrew, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Pinkston, Lucy L., 1980 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Price, Richard, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Reisman, Robert, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Rostkowski, Charlene, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Sarfaty, Deborah, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      1952-`
    - Schenkein, Ronnie, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Scherr, Les, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Schulman, David J., 1980 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Siegler, Larry, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Simoncini, Diane C., 1980 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Stockwell, David C., 1980 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Tintle, Kevin L., 1980 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Walsh, Maureen Ann, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Wilkinson, J. Erby, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Yanoff, Susan R., 1980 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Adsit, Jane C., 1981 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Bachman, Diane, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Barta, Mary Alice, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Bates, Wendy A., 1981 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Bloomquist, Charles R., 1981 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Brewster, Dennis M., 1981 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Brooks, Marjory, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Brothers, Sherry L., 1981 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Budik, Louis W., 1981 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Chase, Thomas H., 1981 (Box 23, Folder 42)
      1953-2010
    - Christiansen, Daniel J., 1981 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Clark, David M., 1981 (Box 23, Folder 44)